corbis.com 2000-10-10

# Corbis - Help

At Corbis, we understand and respect your concern about the privacy of any information you supply while at our site. We believe that knowledge is the key to monitoring and protecting how your information is used on the Internet. This statement sets forth Corbis' Privacy Policy and describes the practice Corbis follows with respect to all visitors to this site. Please be aware that the Corbis site contains links to other sites that are covered by their own privacy policies. 

**Personal Information**   
To become a Corbis member, you must provide some basic name and contact information. Corbis uses this information for internal purposes: to process your order, to maintain or update your Corbis account, or to send you updates about special offers, new services, special promotions, and noteworthy news and events. **Corbis does not sell or rent information about our customers to third parties**. Corbis may share this information with Corbis' partners or affiliates to enable them to provide you with special benefits, offers, or promotions. Additionally, Corbis offers its members the choice to not receive e-mails or updates about special benefits, promotions, or offers from either Corbis, its affiliates, or its partners. If you no longer wish to receive these updates, or to unsubscribe from Corbis membership, go to <http://www.corbis.com/mycorbis/unsubscribe.asp> and fill out the necessary information. This will remove you from our mailing list. 

Your profile information (such as age and gender) in the registration form is used by Corbis to create personalized content, services, and advertising on the Corbis Web site. Corbis may also profile your Web site activity in order to accurately track your account and provide you with Corbis products and services that correspond to your interests. Corbis may also compile data in aggregate form so that we may better understand the users that are visiting our site. For example, we may produce reports on the most popular search terms by collecting general search term data based on individual searches. Aggregate data is anonymous and does not contain any personal information that identifies a user. 

**Change of Address or Contact Information**   
If your e-mail address or contact information has changed or is incorrect, you may update or correct this information by sending your information via our [Feedback](http://www.corbis.com/help/feedback.asp) link located in the bottom navigational bar. Or, you can also go to [http://store.corbis.com](http://store.corbis.com/), click My Account, and change your personal information. 

**Security**   
Corbis has a number of technological and operational security functions in place to protect the confidentiality of personal information. However, perfect security on the Internet does not exist. 

All payment information that you submit to Corbis is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology. If you use the payment services of our partner Qpass, your payment information is sent directly to Qpass and is not disclosed to Corbis or any third party. Please consult the Qpass privacy policy for questions about their use of your payment information. 

**Cookies**   
When you visit the Corbis site, Corbis may send your computer a "cookie," a small file that resides on your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow Corbis to make its Web site more useful by storing information about your preferences. For example, if you select images and add them to a portfolio, Corbis will send your computer a cookie that identifies the images you have placed in your portfolio. Cookies do not identify an Internet user, although they do identify a user's computer. You can set your browser's option not to accept cookies, though you may not be able to access all of the features of the Corbis site. 

**E-mail**   
Corbis does not rent or sell e-mail lists. Corbis may send you e-mail to notify you about your recent order or to advise you when someone has received your e-card; this will be sent to the e-mail address you provide to Corbis. Corbis may also send you e-mail with information about Corbis' offers, updates, and features, and those of our affiliates and partners. If you no longer wish to receive these updates or to unsubscribe from Corbis membership, go to <http://www.corbis.com/mycorbis/unsubscribe.asp> and fill out the necessary information. This will remove you from our mailing list. 

**Advertisers on Corbis.com**   
Corbis works with a third party, a company called Flycast, which serves ads to this site. To find out more about how Flycast manages the privacy of information in conjunction with serving ads on this site, please go to [http://www.flycast.com/about_us/index.cfm?sub=pri&content=privacy](http://www.flycast.com/about_us/index.cfm?sub=pri&content=privacy). 

If you have questions about Corbis' privacy policy or concerns about personal information you have supplied to Corbis, please contact our Customer Service Manager at (888) 829-0722 or [storecs@corbis.com](mailto:storecs@corbis.com). 

Back To Top
